androidrootguide.com 2017-12-21

# Privacy Policy Of Android Root Guides

In case you need any more information or if you have any queries or questions about our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to shoot us an email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

At Androidrootguide.com, the privacy of our visitors is of utmost importance and we have made it our top priority. This privacy policy document elucidates how your personal information is received, collated, and utilized by Androidrootguide.com. 

## Log Files

Like scores of other websites on the net, [Androidrootguide.com](http://www.androidrootguide.com/) makes use of log files. The point of a log file is to keep track of what is happening. If something should malfunction within the system, there may be no other way of identifying the problem. Log files are also used to keep track of complex systems, so that when a problem does occur, it is easy to pinpoint and fix. The information inside the log file includes internet protocol or IP addresses, the kind of browser used, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to research trends, administrate the site, track an user’s movement around the site, and glean demographic information. IP addresses and other pertinent information are not linked to anything that is personally identifiable or traceable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Androidrootguide.com does use cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences, record user-specific information from pages the user accesses, customize webpage content based on a visitor’s browser type or other information that a visitor sends via his or her browser.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Androidrootguide.com.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Androidrootguide.com and other sites on the net.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense among others.

These third party advertisement servers or advertisement networks use technology on their advertisements and links that appear on Androidrootguide.com sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) may also be utilized by the third party advertisement networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertised matter that you see.

Androidrootguide.com has no access or control over these cookies that are used by such third party advertising agencies. 

It is prudent to consult the respective privacy policies of these third party advertisement servers for detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions on how to opt out of certain policies and practices. Androidrootguide.com’s privacy policy does not apply to the activities of such advertisers or websites as it is beyond our control.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through the options tab on your browser. More information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browser’s respective websites. We would advise you to go through the same for better clarity and transparency.
